LUKE BONO

Oviedo, FL · (407) 272-7103 · LABORLFL@YAHOO.COM ·

I am very enthusiastic about getting into a job in Game Design and Development in my future. I am well experienced with customers/gussets, and I have excellent communication skills because of it. My knowledge on computers, and most electronics, is vast which includes both Hardware and Software.

EXPERIENCE

SEPTEMBER 2018 - DECEMBER 2018

STOCKER, UNIVERSAL STUDIOS ORLANDO FLORIDA

I made sure that all locations assigned had fresh stock of all food and drink products throughout my shift as well as made sure to clean up/restock my areas prior to the next shift.

SEPTEMBER 2019 - OCTOBER 2019

SEASONAL HELP, HOBBY LOBBY

Assisted the Frame Shop in repairing picture frames and broken glass. As well as helped with the unloading process of the weekly truck deliveries.

NOVEMBER 2021 – AUGUST 2022

COOK/CASHIER/PREP, BURGERFI

My job consisted of both making and selling the food. I was to assemble the orders according to the ticket and server them in a timely manner. I was also in charge of taking customer orders using the POS system up front.

AUGUST 2022 - CURENT

CREW MEMBER, CHIPOTLE MEXICAN GRILL

I started off working the FoH making sure the customers had their order correct before moving on as well as made sure all parts to the order are present before checking them out using the POS system.

EDUCATION

MAY 2018

DIPLOMA, LAKE HOWELL HIGH SCHOOL

I graduated with a 3.2 GPA, and was also part of the International Thespian Honor Society and Silver Hawks Gaming League

CURRENTLY ENROLLED

AA, SEMINOLE STATE COLEGE OF FLORIDA

I started back in 2018 and have been enrolled ever since. I am currently going for my AA at SSC then I will soon transfer to UCF to continue getting my Bachelor's in Game Design and Development.

SKILLS

- Basic Microsoft Office
- Advanced Computer/Technical Knowledge
- Conversational American Sign Language
- Moderate HTML and CSS in Web Design

ACTIVITIES

In my spear time I like to work on schoolwork and play video games. Every Monday I play D&D with a group of my friends. I love designing and building computers, two of which I have personally built for myself.